Oh! It's so good! It's so cute! I found it!
Oh! It's a pump! It's so cute! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God! That's amazing! So cute!
Aim for it! Bakemono Master Eno Road Special Edition Okinawa! Yay!
Yes! So, this is a special edition, but we have new friends!
Hello! I'm Yuna Ishibata!
Yay! Yuna! Here she is! Do you like Pokemon?
I love Pokemon! I used to play it a lot when I was little!
Really? But we are the same age! We are of the same generation!
I guess we are! I can't open my eyes!
It's a little too sunny! It's so beautiful!
It's the ocean!
This time, there seem to be some places where Pokemon can be found for Pokegenic photos.
I'm going to wander around looking for them!
Let's go!
It's so beautiful! The weather is too nice!
It looks a bit like Okinawa!
This color is amazing!
This is amazing! The view is so beautiful!
Did I tell you the last time I was here? I went to Okinawa for New Year's.
I found out later that you were actually there.
It was really the same day.
I was in Okinawa with Yama, and Yuna was there with her family.
We went to the same place!
Yes, we did! The weather was so bad! We talked about it.
So I haven't seen such a clear sea in a long time!
At this rate, I'll be able to show you a nice view!
This is American Village!
This is American Village in a place called Chatan.
Have you been here before?
I was here last New Year's!
Really? Yes, yes!
I think I've been in here!
Really? Yes, you have!
Yes, I'm sure! I went into a store on this street!
There are a lot of stores by the sea.
It's nice to see the ocean!
It's nice, isn't it? I've been in my hometown for a while.That's great! I've been in my hometown a lot.
Oh! There he is! There he is!
Oh, my gosh! There's so many of them!
Ta-da! I found it!
Isn't he so cute?
So cute!
It's amazing!
It looks like it's from overseas!
Yes, it is! It's like overseas! So stylish!
Do you want to take a picture of this?
Let's take a picture! Let's take a picture!
Ready! Okay!
Okay, thank you!
There's a little arrow in the picture.
Is there? I don't know.
Oh! Oh! There it is!
There it is! There it is! Let's go!
Oh, my God! So many!
Oh, my God! Oh! There's suits!
Oh, my God! Really! It's so cute!
Oh, wow! Oh, my God!
That's amazing!
Ta-da!
There's Pikachu!
So cute!
Hey, stand here!
How do I take a picture of this?
Ah! Good! Good!
Oh! It's so good!
It's so cute!
That's nice!
That's awesome!
Let's take lots of pictures!
This one's good, too!
It's so cute!
I love the way he's sitting!
Speaking of Pikachu, Lilia!Speaking of Pikachu, Lilia.
Really?
Wow, thank you.
Here you go. Cheese.
That's so cool!
It's so good! It's so cute!
Same height.
That's for sure, that's for sure.
It's so good!
Thank you very much.
I'm chenik.
Shall we go to the other side?
Sure, there's an arrow here, so let's go there.
Is it up there?
But there are footprints.
Yes, it's definitely up there.
Let's go up.
I wonder where it is.
It's so hot.
I'm drenched in sweat.
I think this might be my first time in Okinawa in the summer.
Really?
January.
This is it!
I can hold a balloon!
Great, I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
Really? Yes!
That's so cute.
I like it.
Oh, you can stand up.
Oh, it's cute.
Yay!
Oh, it looks good.
Here you go. Cheese.
Wow.
It's so cute!
Wow, so cute!
Thank you so much.Thank you very much.
Oh, there's more?
It's still going.
I thought that was here.
Well, then it's in the middle of something, isn't it?
Oh, no. But it's already here.
Huh? Where is it?
What?
Oh, there he is.
Arrow.
Oh, yeah.
Pokégenic
Not yet.
It's true.
Eh, it's a lot of fun.
It's fun.
What?
This place?
This place is so cool.
Yeah, it is.
This is a great location.
This place looks great.
It's gonna look great.
Where are you?
Where's the view?
Blue?
Blue Seal.
I'm at the Blue Seal.
I'm on Blue Seal.
Oh, here.
Oh, there they are, there they are.
Oh, my gosh!
I just did it.I'm home!
in Okinawa
Arrows
What?
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here!
It's hiding really well.
Wait a minute... not too much, but...
Tails?
Just a tail?
It's so cute.
Oh, a tail.
Oh, it's hiding.
Heh.
Does it look amazing?
A tail.
There he is.
He's hiding.
It's hiding.
Okay, let's go up there.
Let's go upstairs.
It smells so good.
It smells delicious.
Pokégenic.
You mean this way? Okay, then.
Okay.
This way.
What?
Huh? You there?
Where are you?
We're lost.
But there are footprints.
Oh, my God.
You're in the shadows.
You're here.
No, not there.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, my God.That's great.
There it is.
Budfrey.
Oh, wow!
You mean I can be a Pokémon too?
It's a bounce-in type of thing.
It's the bounce-in type.
Okay, I'll take a picture.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
You've got bounce, Lilia.
Yay!
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, it's so good!
It looks good on you.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh!
That's nice.
Amazing.
That's so cute.
It's so cute.
Wow, that's a nice reflection.
Thank you very much.
I took some pictures.
I'm actually recommending a place.
Let's go.
This way.
Ta-da!
Is this it?
That's it.
Oh, here it is.
Here it is.
It's just noon.
Let's have lunch.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Excuse me.Excuse me.
Eh, what would you like?
It might be my first time.
Oh, no? Really?
I walk by your restaurant all the time and it looks delicious.
Really? - Yeah.
I'd like you to try it.
Do you have any recommendations?
Well, I don't have any recommendations.
Well, the standard...
Houtama.
And abura-miso (soybean paste).
Aburimiso?
Delicious!
Only in Okinawa
I don't know.
Yamaori Minori for sure.
Maybe not in other regions.
It's hard to decide.
There are so many kinds.
I'll try the standard one sometimes.
I'll have the standard one too.
Two...
Two Houmatama.
And I'll order a drink.
Yes, of course.
This looks delicious.
Sanshincha lemon.
Yes, two of those too.
Two of those, please.
That's what I said.
It's ready!
I drank it.
First of all, the juice.
It's not juice, it's tea.
Sanshincha.
Sanshincha.three types of tea
and
Onigiri (rice ball)
Ta-da!
It's so warm!
Warm!
Freshly made
Smells good.
It smells good. - Really?
Please.
I don't know... pork and egg rice balls aren't very common in Tokyo.
It's not that common in Tokyo.
In Okinawa, it's popular and standard.
It's also used on field trips.
Sometimes it's a bento box lunch
A big pork and egg onigiri
with a big pork and egg onigiri.
I really liked the way my mom made them.
Do you have a family recipe?
Maybe some.
A little.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
Looks good!
Smells great.
Oh, my gosh!
Two for life!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
This is it.
Delicious.
The eggs are a little bit sweet and delicious.
I love it.
Really? It's good.
It's very nostalgic.
It's amazing.
Do you like Okinawan food?Do you have a favorite Okinawan dish?
Kaze Chanpuru
I like it.
I like Goe too.
Kaze Chanpuru is delicious, isn't it?
And carrots.
Do you know them?
I love carrots.
I know.
It's like home cooking.
Whenever I find an Okinawan restaurant, I want to go in.
Really?
That makes me happy.
It's good, isn't it?
You ate it.
I want to come back.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
I'm sure there's more.
It's so unobtrusive, you'd never know it was there.
Footprints are important.
There's a lot of footprints.
I want to ride this.
I wonder what this is.
It's from overseas.
You see them sometimes, don't you?
It's amazing!
It's so beautiful!
I love Okinawa!
It's right around summer vacation.
There it is.
There's a sign.
You mean there's two more?
I found them.
It's so cute.
Can you guys tell?
Metamon is a pedestrian crossing.
So cute.Cute.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing. It's so foreign. If you just look here.
There's footprints over there.
Shall we go there? Let's go.
I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait.
It goes on and on.
It goes like this. It goes like this.
Looks like it's been in here once.
You mean the Pokemon in the grass?
But it's stopped.
Where?
Where is it?
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
I feel like we're gonna walk right past it.
You wouldn't notice it, would you?
Metamon is on the bench.
Amazing.
Let's sit on it.
You have this, don't you?
I like it. It's the color of the sky.
It's so cute.
Oh, my God.
That's nice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It's so good.
It's so cute.
That's great.
What's your favorite Pokémon?
Can't decide.
I can't decide.
Lucarion.
Summer is the time.
I like cool stuff.I like cool stuff.
What do you like?
I like Shamy.
It's like Shamy.
I used to make caraben and stuff for my mom.
Really? That's amazing.
It's like Shaymini or Jiří Bělohlávek.
He had a stuffed animal.
Seriously?
It's a Happy Set from McDonald's.
I used to collect them when I had Pokemon.
You're taking your DS with you.
I'm going.
I took my DS.
I bought all the DS cassettes.
Really? Really?
I don't play XY or anything.
Maybe I didn't play XY.
I mean, I played Blofor and stuff like that.
I'm from the Bla Foa generation.
Bratina or Black and White?
Which one was it?
I think it was Black.
I think it was Reshiram.
Zekrom and Reshiram.
Yes, yes...
Pokemon is coming out with new characters all the time.
I'm sure...
How many Pokemon are there now? There are so many.
All of them together...
How many are there?
Quite a few.
Violet, Scarlett.
There's so many more.
Who? It's like...
They're all so cute.
I have a younger sister and a younger brother in elementary school.
I used to use my Pokekas.I've been using my Pokémon.
They're all using them right now.
They're cute. They're really nice.
I bought another one earlier today.
Pokekas.
For my brothers.
Souvenirs.
You were here a long time ago, weren't you?
I used to come here a lot.
I used to come here to shop.
Like these clothing stores.
American clothing stores.
There are many of them.
They came to buy.
What's it like to be from Okinawa?
What do you mean? But...
A hometown is a hometown.
That's right.
That's why you're in Chiba, right?
Same here.
It's a little far.
But it is, isn't it?
It's not like we're special.
It's my hometown.
But it's so close to the beautiful ocean.
The ocean is beautiful, too.
I didn't have the ocean nearby.
It was inside.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
It's true, Chiba has an ocean too.
Okinawa is beautiful, isn't it?
Okinawa is nice.
I'll go this way.
Go this way.
Is that a shadow?
It's a shadow.
So you're saying there's someone here? Come on.
Let's find out.Let's look for it.
Arrow over here.
You think he's in there?
It's orange. I thought you might use that.
It looks a little bit like that.
Is this it?
Where?
Oh! It's a match!
He's cute!
Can you see it?
Ta-da!
So cute!
This is cute.
Here it is.
I like it. It's cute.
It goes next to the sleeping one, too.
Cute.
Here you go. Thank you.
Very nice.
Cute.
Hot Tail
That's true.
I'm gonna get burned.
It's so ridiculously hot.
I've been wondering about this place for a while.
I'll go there.
Let's go.
Where is it?
Right here.
The ice cream shop.
It's an ice cream shop.
It's so cool.
It's so cool!
I don't know.
There's a Brucile ice cream shop in Okinawa, right?
You know, the kind they make sandwiches with it.
You can eat it!You can eat it.
Not great.
Pick two cookies.
You pick your favorite ice cream.
You can choose your toppings.
It's customizable.
That's great.
What should we do?
I don't know.
I don't know what I want.
But I can't decide between strawberry or chinsuko.
Both look delicious!
But I couldn't decide between the chinsuko.
Okay, I'll have some!
There you go!
So cute!
What did you choose?
I got the flying Pikachu ice cream.
and the cookie is a plain one.
and the topping is a color spray!
I like it.
So cute!
I got the red potato tin scotch flavor
Strawberry.
Hibiscus mango
I made it refreshing.
It's nice... it's definitely summery.
Summer.
What a girl!
Isn't she so cute?
This one itself looks really old-fashioned.
Bon appétit!
Mmmm
hmmm
Mmmm...
It's so good!
Ice cream is so good.
It's so hot.Because it's hot.
It tastes even better.
It's perfect for summer.
It's like this.
What's new?
It's amazing!
It's new!
Bon appétit!
Oh, really!
Yes, it's good.
It's delicious.
It's so good.
No way.
Red potatoes.
I didn't eat the sweet potato one.
That's amazing!
Mmm...
Yeah.
It's Blue Seal, after all.
Yeah, it's good.
Delicious.
Speaking of Okinawa.
Yes. - Yes.
Speaking of Okinawa...
Yes, but this time...
As a new member...
Yuna came to join us.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no...
On the contrary...
If you're okay with it...
Me too.
I'm from Okinawa and I'm a Pokemon.
Are you saying it's okay that I'm like that?
Not at all.
I came with my heart.
I'm so happy!
But I don't know, from the point of view of someone who's watching.But from the perspective of someone who's looking at something
Maybe it's unusual.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe not so much.
But we're the same age.
You know...
So it's really easy to talk to him.
It's really...
I'm glad.
I thought you were easy to talk to.
I'm so happy.
I mean, you're my senior.
I don't think you have to be so self-conscious.
But you do have to be careful, being a junior.
I'm glad you feel that way.
But we're next to each other.
I see.
That's right.
We're right next to each other.
We're next to each other.
We've been talking a lot.
More than before.
But you said you played Pokemon cards.
Your brother...
A younger brother?
Aren't you interested?
But I used to play too.
Oh, really?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I'm interested.
I like to open them.
I really do.
I tried to make a video of opening the package.
I tried it.And I've tried.
Of course it's fun to do it, but
I don't know what's going to come out of it.
the most
No, I know, I know.
I like it.
Let's do it sometime.
Can we?
Sure, of course.
I'd love to.
I want to increase the population.
Someday, I'd like to have a battle.
I want to be good at it.
Gah!
I ate some ice cream and I'm all tuckered out.
I'm all tuckered out.
Let's go look for him.
There.
Oh, and a heart.
A heart!
It's so cute!
I love it. What's the vibe?
It's like...
It's a live radio show.
It's so cute.
It's so cute!
Stylish.
This is nice.
I love it.
It's looking really good right now.
It really is.
Is it over there?
It looks like it's over there.
Shall we go?
Let's go there.
Look at that!
It's so cute!cute little picture
Cute.
There's a lot of them.
Lovekas.
Cute.
They're so cute.
They're like a bouquet.
And there's another one over here.
Who's there?
So cute!
Cute!
You should stand right here in the middle.
I mean, it's okay.
Okay, I'll hold that for you.
Thank you.
It's perfect.
Wait, that's perfect.
It's cute.
That's great.
Blue sky
I love it!
The colors are great!
Oh, it's so nice!
It's just right!
Cute!
It's nice.
Cute, surrounded by cute, looks good. Thank you. I wonder if there are any more of you here.
Oh, my God, it's so cute!
That's amazing. There's no room to get in. What about this one?
How about this? I'd like to squat down for a second.
Where's the eyeball? Show us the eyeball. It's so cute!
That's so cute! I'm going to get methane. It's so cute!
Where's the eyeball?
Where? What? Oh, but it's going great. It's going great.
Sorry, they're here.
Oh, they look great.Oh, it's nice.
Surprisingly assertive.
Cute.
He's surrounded by so many people. He's so happy.
He's so cute all by himself.
Oh, wow, wow.
He's surrounded by so many people.
It's so cute.
He's so cute.
So cute.
It's like the girls in the middle are talking to each other. They're so happy.
Oh, spiky kisses!
Oh, it's a little giraffe!
Oh, they're so cute!
So cute!
So, how was your visit to various pokegenic spots today?
It was fun!
It made me want to get more and more into Pokemon.
Oh, great! Yes, yes, yes! It was fun!
I'm glad.
I don't get many new friends.
Do you mind if I join?
Oh, yeah, of course.
I'd love to keep in touch with you.
Yay, yay, yay.
Then please keep doing it.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
See you soon.
Bye bye.
See you later.
I've always had this image of Lilia and Pokemon together... as if she were a Pikachu.
I can't believe she's playing "Nagarembo.
You were on a singing show, right?
Yeah, wow.
I saw it on TV, and I was a fan.
I was a fan. - Oh, you weren't in it then?
You were such a fan?Were you such a fan?
I don't think so.
I was just looking at her, thinking, "Wow, there's a pretty girl.
I didn't expect to be eating ice cream next to her.
I'm eating ice cream.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah